fontsinuse.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy - Fonts In Use

This privacy policy is here to inform those who are concerned with how their “Personally Identifiable Information” (PII) is being used online.

PII is information that can be used on its own, or with other information, to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information on our website.

**Can I use this website without providing any personal information?**

Yes. You are free to browse the website without providing any personal information.

**What personal information do we collect from visitors to our website?**

When using forms on this website, you may be asked to enter your name and email address.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register or fill out a form on our site, for example when commenting on content on our site, or sending us a contact message.

**How do we use your information?**

We use your email in order to communicate with you, for example:

  * to reply to you if you send us a contact email
  * to confirm your email address during the registration process
  * to notify registered users only of activity related to any content they may contribute to our site
  * to notify users should any form of data breach or security issue arise

Note that all notifications can be turned off in your settings (registered users only).

**How do we protect your information?**

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

For instance, we use cookies to help us store and recall your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with an improved service.

We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, please look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off it will disable some of the features of the site.

**Collection of Anonymous Data**

Our website collects a set of anonymous data when anyone accesses our website. This anonymous data is stored in server log files. We do not use this data to draw any conclusions about your identity.

This data may include:

  * the browser types and versions used
  * the operating system used by the accessing system
  * the website from which an accessing system reaches our website (so-called referrers)
  * the page accessed
  * the date and time of access to the Internet site
  * an Internet protocol address (IP address)
  * similar anonymous data that may be used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.

This data is required to

  * deliver the content of our website correctly
  * optimize the content of our website
  * ensure the long-term viability of our information technology systems and website technology
  * provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a cyber-attack.

We may analyze this anonymous data statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data security of our enterprise, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the personal data we process. The server log files are stored separately from any personal data which you may provide.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

This does not include any parties who assist us in operating and developing our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may release information when it's release is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include links to third-party products or services on our website (for example font vendors). These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics on our website to compile anonymous data regarding user interactions with our website.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

According to CalOPPA (see <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>) , we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
  * You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.
  * Registered users can change their personal information by logging in to your account

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We do not honor “Do Not Track” signals as we have not yet implemented the necessary technical measures.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**Fair Information Practices**

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  * We will notify you via email within 7 business days
  * We will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Fonts In Use LLC  
5321 Miles Ave, Unit Y  
Oakland, California 94618  
The United States of America

info@fontsinuse.com
